http://www.plasticpolybags.com/privacy.php

Loading... Please wait...
Pallet Covers / Gaylord Liners
Trash Bags (Black and Clear)
Add To Cart
Privacy and Security at PlasticPolyBags.comIs your checkout process secure?Yes, shopping at PlasticPolyBags.com is safe. Our secure socket layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts your credit card number so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet.PrivacyWe understand and share your concern about protecting your privacy while shopping online. We want to assure you that PlasticPolyBags.com respects your privacy and treats your personal information with the highest standards of safety, security and confidentiality. To help you feel more comfortable about how we protect your privacy, we provide this document explaining our online information practices.What information does PlasticPolyBags.com collect? Automatic Information We automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on our site. We use this information to analyze our users behavior, interests, and demographics to better understand and serve our shoppers. This information may include the URL that you just came from, what browser you are using, and your IP address. What about Cookies?
Cookies are small pieces of information that a web site will store on your computers hard drive. PlasticPolyBags.com will use cookies to identify you during your session, make our services easier to use and to store items in your shopping cart between visits. Cookies are never used to store sensitive customer information such as names, addresses, credit card numbers or passwords. Acceptance of cookies is not a requirement to browse our site, however our shopping cart does require the acceptance of cookies to work properly. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can configure your browser to prevent that. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies is completely anonymous. Personally Identifiable InformationThis is information that you provide to us that is specific to you. We collect information such as your name, phone number, billing information, shipping information and other personal information as indicated on the forms throughout our site. You provide such information when you make a purchase, enter a contest or sweepstakes, fill out a survey or form, provide product reviews, etc. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You can always choose not to provide information, but you may not be able to use a particular service or feature. We will not sell, trade, or rent any of your personal information to any third party. How do we use your information?
E-mailsIt is possible to register as a PlasticPolyBags.com email subscriber directly from our site. Upon registering, we will periodically send you newsletters featuring sales and product information. When you make a purchase onPlasticPolyBags.comyou will be sent order and shipping confirmation emails.Do we share the information we receive? Checkout During the order process, we will share your information with other necessary parties (banks, shipping companies, etc.) to verify, process and ship your order. Legal RequestsPlasticPolyBags.com will always cooperate with law enforcement inquiries. PlasticPolyBags.com reserves the right to disclose any activities or information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, determine necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or you to legal liability.
Customer Service
Quote Request
Privacy Notice
Shipping and Returns
Sitemap
Stretch Wrap Supplies:
Stretch Wrap
News
Thanksgiving Leftovers
Freezing Thanksgiving Leftovers are more important to sixty five percent of …
